https://www.ccyoung.org/privacy-policy/

COVID-19: HELP SUPPORT CC YOUNG AND OUR EFFORTS TO ENRICH THE LIVES OUR RESIDENTS AND COMMUNITY. Covid Updates Donate Today
Independent LivingResidencesCalendarIndependent Living FAQTestimonialsAssisted LivingResidencesCalendarAssisted Living FAQTestimonialsMemory SupportResidencesCalendarsAdult Day CenterMemory Support FAQHealthcareRehabilitationSkilled NursingIn Home CareAquatics TherapyThe Campus ClinicPalliative CareCalendarsHealthcare FAQAmenitiesDiningSenior Life MinistryThe Point & PavilionThe Point CalendarSenior Tech ClassesMassage TherapyInnovationAboutCOVID-19 CommunicationsOur StoryLeadershipCareersGalleryWhat’s NearbyVolunteerEventsReviewsTestimonialsDevelopmentAuxiliaryBody Mind Spirit ConnectionPlanned GivingDonate NowGift ShopTerraces Expansion ProjectNewsSchedule a TourContactImportant Numbers
Schedule a Virtual Tour Important NumbersTerraces Expansion ProjectNewsContactIndependent LivingResidencesCalendarIndependent Living FAQTestimonialsAssisted LivingResidencesCalendarAssisted Living FAQTestimonialsMemory SupportResidencesCalendarsAdult Day CenterMemory Support FAQHealthcareRehabilitationSkilled NursingIn Home CareAquatics TherapyThe Campus ClinicPalliative CareCalendarsHealthcare FAQAmenitiesGift ShopDiningSenior Life MinistryThe Point & PavilionThe Point CalendarSenior Tech ClassesMassage TherapyInnovationAboutCOVID-19 CommunicationsOur StoryLeadershipCareersGalleryWhat’s NearbyVolunteerEventsReviewsTestimonialsDevelopmentGift ShopAuxiliaryBody Mind Spirit ConnectionPlanned GivingDonate Now Privacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyCC Young is committed to protecting your privacy when you visit our Web site. Information we collect from you is used to improve our site, provide you a better experience, respond to your questions and process your online donations.INFORMATION COLLECTIONWe collect two types of information on our Web site:Web server traffic information. This information is used to determine the number of visitors to our site, length of stay and sources of traffic. We collect aggregate data — or totals of those visiting from a domain — not information identifying individual users. We use this information to help improve our site and our service to you.Personal information provided by you. We collect e-mail addresses and other personal information only when you provide it to us. If you fill out a form or survey, request information or make a donation, we may collect your name, address, city, state, zip code, telephone number and e-mail address.USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATIONCC Young collects information on our Web site. We do not sell, trade or rent our Web site visitors’ personal information to others other than those outlined in this section. If you willingly provide us your personal information, CC Young may use it in the following ways:Donations. When you make an online donation to us, it’s possible your name may be on our mailing lists. As a donor, you may request to have your name removed from our mailing lists. See the Your Choice section below to learn how.E-mail Information Requests and Questions. When we respond to your e-mail requests or questions, we may collect your e-mail address and send you CC Young e-mail bulletins or news. To opt out and remove your name from future e-mails of this type, follow the unsubscribe instructions in the message. E-News: When you sign up to receive CC Young’s e-news, we collect your e-mail address and may also notify you about other information we think you will find valuable. To opt out and remove your name from future e-mails of this type, follow the unsubscribe instructions in the message.YOUR CONSENTBy using CC Young’s website, you consent to the collection and use of the information described above. Any changes to this policy will be posted prior to their implementation.YOUR CHOICEWe respect your privacy and recognize that you may wish to limit the ways in which we contact you. Simply send an e-mail to ccy@ccyoung.org with the following information:To remove your name from our mailing list please provide your full name, mailing address and a sentence requesting removal.To remove your name from our email mailing list please provide your full name, email address and a sentence requesting removal.To review or correct your personal information with CC Young please provide your name and a sentence requesting a review or a correction.SECURITYWe take every precaution to protect your personal information. At CC Young, your personal information is kept confidential and stored in a secure environment. Access to your information is restricted only to authorized staff with a legitimate and specific business purpose. If you have any questions about the security of our Web site, please contact us.Experience the best in dallas Senior living.Schedule a virtual tour of our beautiful community today.
(214) 258-4000
contact us online**** *Web Inquiry is For*Independent LivingAssisted LivingMemory CareSkilled NursingRehabilitationHome HealthHospiceHome ServicesAdult Day CareVolunteersEmploymentActivitiesThe Point & PavilionAuxiliary MembershipDonationMind, Body, Spirit ConnectionOtherNameThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
All faiths welcome Get In Touch4847 West Lawther Drive, Suite 100Dallas, Texas 75214Main Phone: 214-827-8080Sales & Tours: (214) 258-4000
Quick LinksWeekend Manager HandbookResident LoginEmployee LoginCareersApplication for ResidencyMedicare/Insurance Admission© Copyright 2020 CC YoungPrivacy PolicyNotice of Non-Discrimination
